https://www.bankofthesierra.com/privacy/

PRIVACY POLICY
Visitors to Bank of the Sierra’s website remain anonymous. We do not collect unique identifying information about you individually, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us that information.  Our website does collect certain information using “cookies”.  Cookies are small files that your browser places on your computer.  We may use session cookies, persistent cookies, and other tracking technologies such as pixels and tags to better understand how you interact with our site, to monitor usage by our users and web traffic routing on our services, and to improve and personalize our site.  Many internet browsers automatically accept cookies.  You may be able to instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the sites you visit. Google provides some additional privacy options relating to Google analytics, described at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.   We do not respond to “do not track” browser signals at this time.  You may elect to provide us with more specific information, such as when you give us feedback or send us an email.  If you provide us this information, it is used internally and in furtherance of the purpose for which it was provided.  We do not sell information we collect or that is provided to us regarding visitors to Bank of the Sierra’s website to any third parties, and although we do use it for marketing purposes, we would never Spam someone who previously visited our website.
If you believe any of the information is in error, or believe any information collected about you has been used for an improper purpose, please contact Customer Service immediately at 1-888-454-BANK.
Links:
Bank of the Sierra has a number of links to other sites.  These are offered as a courtesy and a convenience.  Bank of the Sierra assumes no responsibility for the content, safety, security or privacy of any such site or any transactions with respect thereto.  If you have questions or concerns about any other site’s policy regarding these matters, you should contact that site or its sponsor.
Amendments and Changes:
Bank of the Sierra reserves the right to amend or change this policy at any time and without notice.  For the most current version of this policy, contact our customer service department at 1-888-454-BANK or visit us online at www.bankofthesierra.com
CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT
Effective 01/01/2020
Information for California Residents
California Consumers’ Rights and Choices
If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request Information regarding the:
Categories of Personal Information (as defined by applicable California law) collected, sold or disclosed by us;
Purposes for which categories of Personal Information collected by us are used;
Sources of information from which we collect Personal Information; and
Specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
In addition, if you are a California resident you may:
Opt-out of the sale or disclosure of your Personal Information, in some circumstances;
Opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us; however, you may still receive administrative communications regarding the Services;
Opt-in to certain financial incentive programs we may offer related to the collection, sale, or deletion of your Personal Information; and
Request deletion of your Personal Information by us and our service providers, in some circumstances.
You will not be discriminated against for exercising your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act.
Collection of Personal Information from California Residents
We have listed below the personal information we may have collected from California residents in the past 12 months.
Category of personal information we may collect: Identifiers
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Identifiers” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Identifiers” include:
To perform services including maintaining or servicing accounts, provide customer service, process transactions or payments, verify customer information, or provide credit/financing.
Category of personal information we may collect: Personal Characteristics
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Personal Characteristics” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Personal Characteristics” include:
To perform services including maintaining or servicing accounts, provide customer service, process transactions or payments, verify customer information, or provide credit/financing.
Category of personal information we may collect: Commercial Information
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Commercial Information” include:
Directly from consumers, Public records from government entities
The purposes for collecting your “Commercial Information” include:
To perform services including maintaining or servicing accounts, provide customer service, process transactions or payments, verify customer information, or provide credit/financing.
Category of personal information we may collect: Internet/Electronic Activity
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Internet/Electronic Activity” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Internet/Electronic Activity” include:
To support internal operations of our website, online banking platform or mobile app or to help detect potential security incidents, and to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity.
Category of personal information we may collect: Geolocational Data
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Geolocational Data” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Geolocational Data” include:
To support internal operations of our website, online banking platform or mobile app or to help detect potential security incidents, and to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity.
Category of personal information we may collect: Sensory Information
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Sensory Information” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Sensory Information” include:
To protect, detect, investigate, report and seek to prevent financial crime
Category of personal information we may collect: Professional Information
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Professional Information” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Professional Information” include:
To access job qualifications if you submitted an application for employment; To open an account or make a loan to you.
Category of personal information we may collect: Educational Information
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Educational Information” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Educational Information” include:
To access job qualifications if you submitted an application for employment; To open an account or make a loan to you.
Category of personal information we may collect: Inferences
Categories of sources from which we may obtain your “Inferences” include:
Directly from consumers
The purposes for collecting your “Inferences” include:
To comply with our regulatory requirements and to offer products and services to you.
Here is information on whether we sell or share your personal information.
Selling/sharing your personal information
Categories of third parties we may sell your personal information to
We do not sell personal information to third parties.
Categories of third parties we may otherwise share your personal information with
Government entities, Third Party Service Providers
Requests
You can make requests related to your California privacy rights at the attached links:
Access My Personal Information
Delete My Personal Information
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
You may also make those requests by calling 1-888-454-2265.
Please be aware that we do not accept or process requests through other means (e.g., via fax, social media, email addresses, etc.).
When you make a request, we will ask you to provide verifying information, such as the phone number on file with the bank and the date and amount of last deposit. We will review the information provided and may request additional information via email or other means to ensure we are interacting with the correct individual.
Please also be aware that making any such request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal or deletion of Personal Information or content you may have posted, and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow us to fulfill your request.
Children
Our Services are not directed to children, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16. If you learn that a child has provided us with Personal Information, then you may contact us as indicated above.
Do Not Track
Bank of the Sierra does not currently take steps to respond to browsers’ “Do Not Track” signals as no uniform standard to respond to such signals has been developed at this time.
If you have any questions or comments about this notice, our Privacy Statement, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California Law, please do not hesitate to contact us at:
Bank of the Sierra
P.O. Box 1930
Porterville, CA 93257
Or by calling 1-888-454-2265
IMPORTANT PRIVACY INFORMATION
Financial Privacy Notice | Notice of Your Financial Privacy Rights
Download the Financial Privacy Notice Here (pdf)
California Opt Out Notice | Important Privacy Choice for Consumers
Download the California Opt Out Notice Here (pdf)
Privacy Policy for Mobile Banking
To opt out:
Fill it out, sign and send back to us at the address provided below (you may want to make a copy for your records):
Mobile Banking Agreement and Disclosure Online Banking Addendum
Footer Information
NEWS
Sierra Bancorp Announces Record Quarterly Earnings
Read More
Need Assistance?
